Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Kathryn and today we've got a monologue.
我是Kathryn，今天我们有一段独白。
We've got one person talking, telling you how to make the perfect sandwich.
有一个人会说话，教你怎么做完美的三明治。
That's right.
没错。
She's a chef and she's going to teach us.
她是一位厨师，她会教我们。
She's going to talk about all the ingredients and some tips on how to make a sandwich.
她会讲到所有食材，以及一些做三明治的小技巧。
So be prepared.
所以做好准备。
This is going to be a really good lesson.
这会是一节非常好的课。
And I'm already hungry thinking about it.
光是想想我就已经饿了。
So let's listen to the dialogue.
那我们来听对话吧。
We'll be back in a moment.
我们一会儿就回来。
Welcome to our show.
欢迎来到我们的节目。
Today I'm going to show you how to make the perfect mouthwatering sandwich.
今天我要教你怎么做一个完美的、让人垂涎欲滴的三明治。
Are you ready?
准备好了吗？
Let's get started.
我们开始吧。
Let's start with the basics.
我们先从基础说起。
Bread.
面包。
Bread is an important ingredient here.
面包是这里很重要的食材。
You need to remember one thing.
你需要记住一件事。
Use the bread according to the following criteria, freshness, crumb and color.
根据以下标准选择面包：新鲜度、面包屑和颜色。
If you want a closed sandwich, I recommend you first toast your bread in a toaster or
如果你想要一个封闭式三明治，我建议你先用烤面包机烤一下面包，或者
oven or grill it slightly until it gets a light brown color.
用烤箱或稍微烤一下，直到它变成浅棕色。
Now that our bread is ready, let's talk about the ingredients.
现在面包准备好了，我们来谈谈食材。
Of course, each person's palate is different, but I'm going to give you a few tips that
当然，每个人的口味不同，但我会给你一些技巧，
you'll be able to use when turning any sandwich into the perfect sandwich.
你可以用它们把任何三明治变成完美的三明治。
I would strongly recommend you put fresh vegetables in your sandwich.
我强烈建议你在三明治里放新鲜蔬菜。
Do not undervalue them as they play a big role in forming the taste and will make the
不要低估它们，因为它们在形成味道中起着重要作用，会让
sandwich more refreshing and light.
三明治更清爽、更轻盈。
The best choices here are evident.
这里最好的选择很明显。
Cucumbers, tomatoes, onions, sweet pepper or chili, lettuce, and of course herbs.
黄瓜、西红柿、洋葱、甜椒或辣椒、生菜，当然还有香草。
You can't go wrong with them.
用它们准没错。
As for aubergines, mushrooms and asparagus, I would recommend you first grill them slightly
至于茄子、蘑菇和芦笋，我建议你先稍微烤一下，
with a little touch of olive oil.
加一点橄榄油。
Last but not least, we have a wide variety of condiments that we can add to our perfect
最后但同样重要的是，我们有各种各样的调味品可以加到我们的完美
sandwich.
三明治里。
We can be subtle and add just a touch of salt and pepper, or we can combine mustard sauce,
我们可以低调一点，只加一点盐和胡椒，或者我们可以混合芥末酱、
mayonnaise, ketchup, or even caviar to achieve a stronger flavor.
蛋黄酱、番茄酱，甚至鱼子酱来获得更浓郁的味道。
It's always a good idea to cut your sandwich in triangles or manageable pieces to avoid
把三明治切成三角形或方便入口的小块总是一个好主意，这样可以避免
all your ingredients falling out and staining your shirt.
所有食材掉出来弄脏你的衬衫。
That's all the time we have for today, but join us next time where we'll be going over
今天的时间就到这里，但下次加入我们，我们会讲解
how to make the perfect lasagna.
如何做完美的千层面。
Till next time!
下次见！
Alright, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So, obviously, I think she knows what she's talking about.
所以，显然，我觉得她知道自己在说什么。
This is going to be a great sandwich.
这会是一个很棒的三明治。
Alright, so she mentioned a lot of ingredients, a couple of different words that we might
好了，她提到了很多食材，还有一些我们可能
not understand.
不认识的词。
So, let's take a look at them now in Language Takeaway.
所以，我们现在在“语言小贴士”环节来看看它们。
Language takeaway.
语言小贴士。
Okay, so let's go.
好的，那我们开始吧。
There's a lot of ingredients in this sandwich.
这个三明治里有很多食材。
You can see the ingredients.
你可以看到这些食材。
So, let's go ahead and take a look at the ingredients.
所以，我们继续来看看这些食材。
Alright, so we have the ingredients here.
好了，我们这里有这些食材。
We have the bread, we have the butter, we have the onions.
我们有面包、黄油、洋葱。
We have the tomatoes.
我们有西红柿。
We have the lettuce.
我们有生菜。
We have the tomatoes.
我们有西红柿。
We have the onions.
我们有洋葱。
We have the lettuce.
我们有生菜。
We have the tomatoes.
我们有西红柿。
We have the onions.
我们有洋葱。
We have some different synonyms that we might not know.
我们有一些可能不认识的同义词。
So, we need to go through the synorms that we might not know.
所以，我们需要过一遍那些可能不认识的同义词。
And she mentioned the word crumb.
她提到了“crumb”这个词。
Okay, yeah. She said freshness, crumb and color.
好的，是的。她说了新鲜度、面包屑和颜色。
So what does she mean by crumb of the bread?
那她说面包的“crumb”是什么意思？
Okay, so crumb, a crumb is a very, very, very, very, very small piece of bread.
好的，“crumb”就是非常非常非常非常小的一块面包。
Like when you put bread in a toaster, maybe it's what falls down actually.
就像你把面包放进烤面包机时，可能掉下来的东西。
We call them bread crumbs sometimes.
我们有时叫它们面包屑。
You can cook with them.
你可以用它们来烹饪。
But they're basically little pieces of bread that fall off, little grains.
但它们基本上就是掉下来的小面包块，小颗粒。
Okay, yeah. So, yeah, usually it happens all the time.
好的，是的。所以，嗯，通常经常发生。
You're having cookies or you're having some bread, you bite into it and little pieces of bread or cookie fall down.
你吃饼干或面包时，咬一口，小块的饼干或面包就会掉下来。
Those are called crumbs.
那些就叫“crumbs”。
That's right. And this is a very...
没错。这是一个非常……
And I want to remind everyone that the word crumb has a B on the end.
我想提醒大家，“crumb”这个词末尾有个B。
C-R-U-M-B. But we don't pronounce the B. We just say crumb.
C-R-U-M-B。但我们不发音那个B，我们只说“crumb”。
Yeah, you don't say crumb.
对，你不会说“面包屑”。
No.
不。
Okay, so just crumb.
好，所以就说“面包屑”。
Yeah, be careful with that one.
嗯，那个词要小心用。
All right. So we have to keep a look out for the crumb of the bread.
好的，所以我们得留意面包的“面包屑”。
I guess how fresh and how... Sometimes when you squeeze bread, it makes a nice little sound.
我想，面包有多新鲜，还有……有时候你捏面包时，它会发出好听的声音。
Crunch, crunch.
嘎吱，嘎吱。
Exactly.
没错。
But she's also recommending a couple of different ingredients.
但她也推荐了几种不同的配料。
And she said, well, it depends on each person's palate.
她说，这取决于每个人的口味。
So after we've chosen our bread, she talks about a closed sandwich and maybe toasting it.
所以选好面包后，她谈到了封闭式三明治，可能还要烤一下。
Okay, so there are two options for sandwiches.
好的，所以三明治有两种选择。
You might see these on menus as well as when you're cooking yourself.
你在菜单上可能会看到这些，自己做饭时也会遇到。
A closed sandwich means you have two pieces of bread, one on the bottom and one on top.
封闭式三明治就是有两片面包，一片在底，一片在顶。
It's closed.
它是封闭的。
Okay.
好的。
But the opposite is an open sandwich.
但相反的是开放式三明治。
That means you only have one piece of bread and then maybe you have some meat on top.
那意味着你只有一片面包，然后在上面放些肉。
Oh, okay. Actually, I always thought that for it to be a sandwich, you had to have two pieces of bread.
哦，好的。其实我一直以为要算三明治，必须有两片面包。
Well, now when you... I would challenge you to look on Google for open-faced sandwich or open sandwich.
嗯，现在你可以……我建议你去谷歌搜一下“open-faced sandwich”或“open sandwich”。
You'll find some very interesting things.
你会发现一些很有趣的东西。
Yeah, I've had them.
是啊，我吃过。
Actually, you can put some meat and some cheese just on top of a piece of bread and you're done.
其实，你可以在面包片上放些肉和奶酪，就搞定了。
I'm a huge fan of those.
我超喜欢那种。
Yeah.
嗯。
So that's a closed sandwich, though, when you have two pieces of bread and the meat in the middle.
所以那是封闭式三明治，有两片面包，肉在中间。
And after that, she talks a little bit about people's tastes and what people want.
之后，她稍微谈到了人们的口味和需求。
But she used a very special word.
但她用了一个很特别的词。
That's right.
没错。
She said each person's palate is different.
她说每个人的“味觉”都不同。
Okay, a palate in the context of food and taste means the way that food flavors affect a person individually.
好的，在食物和味道的语境中，“味觉”指的是食物风味对个人的影响方式。
That's right.
没错。
So sometimes you say that some people have very good palate so they can maybe tell the difference between a wine from 1978 and a wine from 1980 or something like that.
所以有时你会说有些人味觉很灵敏，能分辨出1978年的酒和1980年的酒之类的区别。
That's right.
没错。
So you can have a palate, a good palate for wine, but also in this case, we're talking about food.
所以你可以有对酒的味觉，但在这里，我们讨论的是食物。
I could say I have a very sensitive palate so I don't like to use very, very strong flavors.
我可以说我的味觉很敏感，所以不喜欢用非常强烈的味道。
Okay.
好的。
So the palate is basically your taste.
所以“味觉”基本上就是你的品尝能力。
It's actually a physical part of your mouth.
它其实是你口腔里的一个物理部位。
It's the top of your mouth where your tongue can touch the top of your mouth.
是口腔顶部，你的舌头能碰到的地方。
The roof of your mouth, exactly.
上颚，没错。
It's not just your ability to taste sweet.
它不只是你尝甜味的能力。
It's sweet and salty and sour and all these different flavors.
它涉及甜、咸、酸等各种不同的味道。
Okay.
好的。
So a person's palate.
所以一个人的“味觉”。
Now, herbs, right?
现在，香草，对吧？
Now, moving on to the main ingredients.
现在，我们来说说主要配料。
You mentioned a lot of easy ones like tomatoes, onions, lettuce, but then we got into a little bit more specific things like, for example, this word that's always mispronounced, herbs.
你提到了很多简单的，比如番茄、洋葱、生菜，但后来我们聊到了一些更具体的东西，比如那个总被读错的词——“香草”。
Actually, you can say herbs.
其实，你可以说“herbs”（带h音）。
It's a very British thing to do though.
不过这是很英式的读法。
Americans and Canadians say herbs.
美国人和加拿大人说“erbs”（h不发音）。
It has an H in the front.
它前面有个H。
That's why it's confusing.
这就是为什么容易混淆。
Okay.
好的。
So we can accept basically if somebody says herbs, but I guess in American English, it's more commonly pronounced as a silent H.
所以如果有人读“herbs”，我们基本也能接受，但我想在美式英语里，更常见的是h不发音。
That's right, herbs.
没错，“erbs”。
Herbs.
“Herbs”（带h音）。
And what are herbs, you might be asking.
你可能会问，香草是什么？
Well, herbs can come in many different shapes and sizes.
嗯，香草有各种形状和大小。
They're usually green.
它们通常是绿色的。
They're usually grown.
通常是种植的。
They're ways of giving food different flavors.
它们是给食物增添不同风味的方式。
And so basil, for example, is an herb.
比如罗勒就是一种香草。
It's a big green leaf, something that we use in pesto, for example.
它是一种大绿叶，比如我们做青酱时会用到。
You can also have rosemary or mint.
你还可以有迷迭香或薄荷。
These are all kinds of herbs.
这些都是香草。
Okay.
好的。
Some people even have an herb garden.
有些人甚至有自己的香草园。
That's right.
没错。
They grow their own herbs.
他们自己种香草。
Okay.
好的。
So now moving on to these weird-looking vegetables, for example, aubergines.
现在来说说这些长相奇怪的蔬菜，比如“aubergines”（茄子）。
Okay.
好的。
Aubergines are the same as eggplants.
“Aubergines”和“eggplants”是一样的。
So you might hear this word sometimes.
所以你有时会听到这个词。
It's basically a big purple vegetable.
它基本上是一种紫色的大蔬菜。
Okay.
好的。
So for those of you who haven't seen an aubergine or an eggplant, yeah, it's a big purple vegetable.
所以对于那些没见过“aubergine”或“eggplant”的人来说，是的，它是一种紫色的大蔬菜。
It kind of looks like a cucumber but a little bit fatter.
它看起来有点像黄瓜，但稍微胖一点。
Very fat.
非常胖。
And if you hold them, they're not very hard.
如果你拿着它们，它们并不硬。
They're kind of soft.
它们有点软。
Yeah.
是的。
And a lot of people like to grill these or to cook with them in, for example, Chinese
很多人喜欢烤这些或者用它们烹饪，比如在中餐里，
where there's a lot of eggplant or aubergines.
那里有很多茄子。
All right.
好的。
So we've had those.
所以我们有这些了。
We have mushrooms.
我们有蘑菇。
And what about asparagus?
那芦笋呢？
Asparagus is actually one of my favorite foods but it's very strange-looking.
芦笋其实是我最喜欢的食物之一，但它看起来很奇怪。
It's kind of green and it kind of has this little head, right?
它有点绿，而且顶端有个小头，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
It's long.
它很长。
It's green.
它是绿色的。
It's kind of like a pencil.
它有点像铅笔。
But at the very top, it's kind of like a plant almost.
但在最顶端，它几乎像一株植物。
Yeah.
是的。
They have a very strong taste and many people don't like asparagus.
它们的味道很浓，很多人不喜欢芦笋。
That's right.
没错。
And the Germans, I think, actually, Germans and the Dutch have special asparagus that's white.
而且我觉得德国人，实际上德国人和荷兰人有种特殊的白色芦笋。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
It's called Spargel.
它叫 Spargel。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
But if any of you know what that is, it's basically a white asparagus.
但如果你们知道那是什么，它基本上就是白色芦笋。
But asparagus is very popular in a lot of parts of the world.
但芦笋在世界很多地方都很受欢迎。
Okay.
好的。
So now we have our vegetables.
所以现在我们有了蔬菜。
We have our bread.
我们有了面包。
But now we need to add a little bit of extra flavor to the sandwich.
但现在我们需要给三明治加一点额外的风味。
So this is where we add some condiments.
这就是我们加调味品的地方。
Okay.
好的。
So condiments are a category.
所以调味品是一个类别。
You can have many different kinds of condiments.
你可以有很多不同种类的调味品。
The most common are salt and pepper.
最常见的是盐和胡椒。
Okay.
好的。
So a condiment is a category of the things that you would add flavor to, as you said, salt, pepper.
所以调味品是你用来增加风味的物品类别，就像你说的，盐、胡椒。
But here they mention, for example, mayonnaise or ketchup.
但这里他们提到，比如蛋黄酱或番茄酱。
Oh, and mustard as well.
哦，还有芥末。
These are all condiments.
这些都是调味品。
So in different parts of the world, they have different kinds of condiments.
所以在世界不同地方，他们有不同种类的调味品。
I've seen, for example, a lot of vinegar in Asia.
我见过，比如在亚洲有很多醋。
You can also have hot pepper flakes like in Europe.
你也可以有辣椒片，比如在欧洲。
Yeah.
是的。
The condiments that you add to your sandwich are varied.
你加在三明治里的调味品种类很多。
I've seen people put all types of condiments in their sandwich.
我见过人们把各种调味品放进三明治里。
And, for example, one that may be a little bit strange or maybe a little bit more expensive condiment is caviar.
而且，比如，一种可能有点奇怪或稍微贵一点的调味品是鱼子酱。
Okay.
好的。
So caviar is not always considered a condiment.
所以鱼子酱不总被认为是调味品。
It can be, but it can also be eaten alone.
它可以算，但也可以单独吃。
But it's basically just fish eggs.
但它基本上就是鱼卵。
They're little fish eggs.
它们是小小的鱼卵。
Very small.
非常小。
It always usually, in people's mind, it's kind of like a fancy food, very luxurious, very expensive.
在人们心目中，它通常是一种高档食物，非常奢华，非常昂贵。
Well, it can be very expensive if you get like beluga caviar.
嗯，如果你买白鲸鱼子酱，那可能非常贵。
A lot of caviar comes from the Caucasus and Russia and Ukraine, these places.
很多鱼子酱来自高加索地区、俄罗斯和乌克兰这些地方。
And it's very, very salty in flavor.
而且它的味道非常非常咸。
That's right.
没错。
So that is also considered a condiment in our case because we're using it for a sandwich, right?
所以在这种情况下，它也被视为调味品，因为我们用它来做三明治，对吧？
Okay.
好的。
So a lot of words there, a lot of interesting things going on in our sandwich.
所以这里有很多词，我们的三明治里有很多有趣的东西。
Why don't we move on now to Fluency Builder where we're going to take a look at some phrases.
我们不如继续到流利度构建部分，在那里我们会看一些短语。
Fluency Builder
流利度构建
All right.
好的。
So let's go back to the very beginning of the dialogue when she said, all right, let's start with the basics.
那么让我们回到对话的最开始，当她说：好的，我们从基础开始。
Okay.
好的。
The basics is a set phrase in this context.
在这个语境中，“基础”是一个固定短语。
We can say this about many different things, but the basics basically refers to the most simple ingredients or the most simple elements.
我们可以对很多不同的事情这么说，但“基础”基本上指的是最简单的原料或最简单的元素。
In this case, bread or meat.
在这种情况下，是面包或肉。
But you can also talk about the basics in other contexts like clothes shopping.
但你也可以在别的语境中谈论“基础”，比如买衣服。
Like when school started when I was a kid, my mom always used to buy me the basics.
比如我小时候开学时，我妈妈总是给我买基础款。
So T-shirts and socks.
所以是T恤和袜子。
Exactly.
没错。
So I guess the basics are the absolute necessary things.
所以我想“基础”是绝对必要的东西。
Yes.
是的。
Right?
对吧？
And also very simple.
而且也非常简单。
So for example, if you talk about dancing, the basics would be maybe a certain sequence of steps that important, essential.
所以比如，如果你谈论跳舞，基础可能是一系列重要的、基本的舞步。
That's right.
没错。
And would caviar be a part of the basics, for example?
那鱼子酱会是基础的一部分吗，比如？
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
No, that's an extra.
不，那是额外的。
Okay.
好的。
So this is what we refer to when we say the basics.
这就是我们说的基础部分。
Now our chef, when she continued talking about her sandwich, she said, I would strongly recommend you use fresh vegetables in your sandwich.
我们的厨师在继续谈论她的三明治时说，我强烈建议你在三明治里放新鲜蔬菜。
Okay, so you can say I would recommend this, but to strongly recommend is to have a very, very strong feeling about something.
好的，所以你可以说“我建议这个”，但“强烈建议”意味着对某件事有非常非常强烈的感觉。
That's right.
没错。
You're saying to the person basically do it.
你基本上是在告诉对方去做。
You must.
你必须做。
Yeah.
是的。
So if maybe your friend is sick, you can say something like, I would strongly recommend you go to the doctor today.
所以如果你的朋友生病了，你可以说，我强烈建议你今天去看医生。
That means you really, really should go to the doctor.
这意味着你真的真的应该去看医生。
I would be upset if you didn't.
如果你不去，我会不高兴的。
It's kind of formal though.
不过这有点正式。
It seems like you would maybe use it with your boss or maybe with a person you don't really know that well, but with your friend you would say, I really think you should go to the doctor.
好像你可能会对老板或不太熟悉的人用，但对朋友你会说，我真的觉得你应该去看医生。
Yeah.
是的。
But you can say it in both contexts, but yeah, definitely more of a formal thing.
但两种场合都可以用，不过确实更正式一些。
Okay.
好的。
So we strongly recommend that you, yeah, okay.
所以我们强烈建议你，嗯，好的。
All right, so now for our last phrase, right?
好了，现在是我们最后一个短语了，对吧？
Where are we?
我们到哪了？
Last but not least.
最后但同样重要。
So now moving on to our next phrase, when she started talking about the condiment, she said, last but not least, we have a wide variety of condiments.
现在进入下一个短语，当她开始谈论调味品时，她说，最后但同样重要，我们有各种各样的调味品。
Okay, this is a very, very common phrase.
好的，这是一个非常非常常见的短语。
It's a set phrase.
这是一个固定短语。
You will hear these words together very often.
你会经常听到这些词一起出现。
Last but not least.
最后但同样重要。
What could this possibly mean?
这可能是什么意思呢？
So obviously last means the last step here.
显然，“最后”指的是这里的最后一步。
The last point.
最后一点。
But why not least?
但为什么不是“不最不重要”？
Well, it's not least important.
嗯，它并不是最不重要的。
Just because it's last, it doesn't mean that it's not important.
仅仅因为它是最后一个，并不意味着它不重要。
Okay, so maybe there are many people who have to give presentations in school and I'm the very, very last person to go.
好的，所以可能有很多人要在学校做演讲，而我是最后一个。
The teacher will say, last but not least, Catherine.
老师会说，最后但同样重要，凯瑟琳。
That's right.
没错。
Makes me feel better.
让我感觉好多了。
Because you're saying you're last, but it doesn't mean you're not important.
因为你说你是最后一个，但这并不意味着你不重要。
Exactly.
正是。
So when you want to make sure that the last point of your presentation or what you're talking about is not ignored or you just want to make sure that everyone knows that it's also very important,
所以当你希望确保你演讲或谈论内容的最后一点不被忽视，或者只是想让大家知道它也很重要时，
you say, last but not least.
你就说，最后但同样重要。
Great.
太好了。
All right, and now last but not least, the end of Fluency Builder.
好了，现在最后但同样重要，流利度构建器结束了。
We're going to close off with this little phrase.
我们将用这个小短语来收尾。
When she was talking about salt and pepper, she said, a touch of salt and pepper.
当她谈到盐和胡椒时，她说，一点点盐和胡椒。
Okay, a touch of salt and pepper is basically a measure.
好的，“一点点盐和胡椒”基本上是一种量度。
It's not a lot.
不是很多。
It's very little amount of salt and pepper.
是非常少量的盐和胡椒。
So we can say a touch.
所以我们可以说“一点点”。
So it's not really a specific quantity though, right?
但它并不是一个具体的数量，对吧？
We're not saying like a spoon of salt and pepper.
我们不是说一勺盐和胡椒。
Not at all.
完全不是。
It basically means a little bit.
它基本上意味着一点点。
A little bit.
一点点。
So you're just saying, maybe you'll hear this in maybe a cooking show or you'll read it in books when they'll say a pinch of salt or a touch of salt or a dash of salt.
所以你可能会在烹饪节目里听到，或者在书里读到，他们会说“一撮盐”或“一点点盐”或“少许盐”。
That's right.
没错。
You could even say it about other things.
你甚至可以用在其他东西上。
For example, if my friend just wrote this article and he wanted me to read it, I say, it's a really good article, but it could use a touch of humor.
比如，如果我朋友刚写了一篇文章，想让我读，我会说，这是一篇很好的文章，但可以加一点点幽默。
I think maybe if you made it a little bit funny, it would be better.
我觉得如果你让它稍微有趣一点，会更好。
Or maybe if you're painting your house, you can say, oh, I think a touch of red paint would look really nice on this wall.
或者如果你在粉刷房子，你可以说，哦，我觉得在这面墙上加一点点红漆会很好看。
That's right. A little bit of red paint would be good.
没错。一点点红漆会很好。
Okay. So a touch of, a really, really good phrase.
好的。所以“一点点”是一个非常好的短语。
It makes you sound very natural.
它让你听起来很自然。
Okay, so that's all the time we have for today.
好的，今天的时间就到这里。
But before we go, let's listen to the dialogue again.
但在我们结束之前，让我们再听一遍对话。
Welcome to our show.
欢迎来到我们的节目。
Today, I'm going to show you how to make the perfect mouthwatering sandwich.
今天，我将教你如何制作完美的令人垂涎的三明治。
Are you ready?
准备好了吗？
Let's get started.
我们开始吧。
Let's start with the basics.
让我们从基础开始。
Bread.
面包。
Bread is an important ingredient here.
面包是这里的重要原料。
You need to remember one thing.
你需要记住一件事。
Choose the bread according to the following criteria.
根据以下标准选择面包。
Freshness, crumb, and color.
新鲜度、面包心和颜色。
If you want a closed sandwich, I recommend you first toast your bread in a toaster or oven or grill it slightly until it gets a light brown color.
如果你想要一个闭合三明治，我建议你先把面包在烤面包机或烤箱里烤一下，或者稍微烤到浅棕色。
Now that our bread is ready, let's talk about the ingredients.
现在面包准备好了，我们来谈谈配料。
Of course, each person's palate is different, but I'm going to give you a few tips that you'll be able to use when turning any sandwich into the perfect sandwich.
当然，每个人的口味不同，但我会给你一些技巧，让你能把任何三明治变成完美的三明治。
I would strongly recommend you put fresh vegetables in your sandwich.
我强烈建议你在三明治里放新鲜蔬菜。
Do not undervalue them as they play a big role in forming the taste and will make the sandwich more refreshing and light.
不要低估它们，因为它们在形成味道方面起着重要作用，会让三明治更清爽、更轻盈。
The best choices here are evident.
这里最好的选择很明显。
Cucumbers, tomatoes, onions, sweet pepper or chili, lettuce, and of course, herbs.
黄瓜、番茄、洋葱、甜椒或辣椒、生菜，当然还有香草。
You can't go wrong with them.
选它们准没错。
As for aubergines, mushrooms, and asparagus, I would recommend you first grill them slightly with a little touch of olive oil.
至于茄子、蘑菇和芦笋，我建议你先用少许橄榄油稍微烤一下。
Last but not least, we have a wide variety of condiments that we can add to our perfect sandwich.
最后但同样重要的是，我们有很多调味品可以加到完美的三明治里。
We can be subtle and add just a touch of salt and pepper, or we can combine mustard sauce, mayonnaise, ketchup, or even caviar to achieve a stronger flavor.
我们可以低调一点，只加一点盐和胡椒，或者混合芥末酱、蛋黄酱、番茄酱，甚至鱼子酱来获得更浓郁的味道。
It's always a good idea to cut your sandwich in triangles or manageable pieces to avoid all your ingredients falling out and staining your shirt.
把三明治切成三角形或方便入口的小块总是一个好主意，这样可以避免所有食材掉出来弄脏你的衬衫。
That's all the time we have for today, but join us next time where we'll be going over how to make the perfect lasagna.
今天的时间就到这里，但下次请加入我们，我们将讨论如何制作完美的千层面。
Till next time!
下次见！
Alright, so talking about sandwich, this really reminds me of making sandwiches at home.
好的，说到三明治，这真的让我想起在家做三明治的情景。
Grilled cheese sandwich. We didn't really talk about it here, but I think it's my favorite sandwich.
烤奶酪三明治。我们这里没怎么提到它，但我觉得它是我最喜欢的三明治。
The grilled cheese sandwich.
烤奶酪三明治。
It's very easy to make. Just two pieces of bread and cheese inside.
做起来很简单。就两片面包，中间夹奶酪。
Do you use butter, though?
但你用黄油吗？
Yes.
用。
So you have to butter the bread, and so when you grill it, it gets really nice and brown.
所以你得在面包上抹黄油，这样烤的时候，它会变得又好看又金黄。
Actually, I'm not a very big sandwich fan when I'm having, for example, a meal like lunch.
实际上，当我在吃午餐之类的正餐时，我不是一个非常喜欢三明治的人。
I don't know. I think I need something more solid than just a sandwich at times.
我不知道。我觉得有时候我需要比三明治更实在的东西。
Interesting. I had a sandwich for dinner last night.
有意思。我昨晚晚餐就吃了一个三明治。
Yeah?
是吗？
I had an egg salad sandwich.
我吃了一个鸡蛋沙拉三明治。
So you had egg salad inside two pieces of bread.
所以你是在两片面包中间夹了鸡蛋沙拉。
That's right, but the bread I had was French bread, so that long, thin bread was very crunchy, very delicious.
没错，但我用的面包是法棍面包，那种又长又细的面包，非常酥脆，非常好吃。
But actually, I like sandwiches for dinner.
但实际上，我喜欢晚餐吃三明治。
They are a little bit lighter.
它们稍微清淡一点。
When you're having a big meal, it just seems like, although maybe sometimes places give you very big, heavy sandwiches
当你吃大餐时，虽然有时候有些地方会给你非常大、非常重的三明治，
that have ham and salami and just a lot of things in there, so they're very, very filling.
里面夹着火腿、萨拉米香肠和很多其他东西，所以它们非常非常管饱。
That's very true. Like a meatball sub, for example, is a very heavy sandwich.
确实如此。比如肉丸潜艇堡，就是一种很重的三明治。
That's right.
没错。
But sandwiches come in all shapes and sizes. You can make basically any sandwich that your brain can think of.
但三明治有各种形状和大小。你基本上可以做出任何你能想到的三明治。
And so we hope that you've learned some words for talking about sandwiches today.
所以我们希望你今天学到了一些谈论三明治的词汇。
Of course, if you have any questions or comments or you want to share with us your very favorite sandwich,
当然，如果你有任何问题或评论，或者想和我们分享你最喜欢的三明治，
you should do so on EnglishPod.com.
你应该在EnglishPod.com上留言。
All right. We'll see you guys there.
好的。我们到时候见。
Bye.
再见。